<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ClydeJohnson]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ClydeJohnson]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 18:02:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The lesson of life ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The lesson of life </h1><p>There once was a man, who was raising his young son. The
mother had passed away in childbirth and he was teaching his
son all that he knew. This son, grew up and in time wanted to
go to a nearby village and find him a companion. Many months
passed and the young man returned to his home, and with him
he had a woman, his wife. They lived in the home of his father.
Shortly after, they had a son. And the father, now a
grandfather, began teaching this young boy all that he
knew: how to respect the forest, the animals and life. The
mother, tiring of sharing her home with the old man,
told her husband that she wanted the old man out.
The father spoke “I cannot; this is his home and he built it for us.”
She spoke, “If you do not make him leave then I will take our son
and I will leave.” The father agreed and spoke to his son. “My son,
tomorrow I want you to take Grandpa out and leave him. Give
him this blanket.” The young boy cried. “Why do you do this?
Grandpa has been teaching me all that I know. Why do I have to
do this to him?” The father spoke. “Son, follow the wishes of your
father.” So the next morning, the father went hunting to the North.
The son took Grandpa as far as he could walk to the South.
That evening the young boy was sitting on the bed crying
when his father came In. He saw the blanket on the bed.
“Son, I thought I told you to give Grandpa the blanket?” “I
gave Grandpa half of the blanket. The other half, I will give
to you some day.” The mother and father understood the
message. And they went and brought Grandpa back.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/remember-to-respect-our-elders/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1c862bd2-f31a-41fc-8b71-54c09ceb5d95</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 18:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will I regret this decision when I'm 80?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Will I regret this decision when I'm 80?</h1><p>I can't help but be inspired by this video. Would I ever regret having tried finding my purpose and enriching the lifes of others?https://youtu.be/jwG_qR6XmDQ  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/will-i-regret-this-decision-when-im-80/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bafe8614-3920-45e3-a021-790cb7cb2a4f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 17:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Started on The Grid]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Getting Started on The Grid</h1><h2>Creating a Site</h2><p>Welcome to The Grid Beta, we’re excited to have you onboard! Here are a few quick tips to get you up and running. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/getting-started-on-the-grid/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c40f9a7c-a447-4ba6-8ed1-e28b0076ea81</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 17:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A little lesson in Karma]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A little lesson in Karma</h1><p>Be careful it may well come back and bite your ass - literally! </p><img src="http://forgifs.com/gallery/d/241917-2/Taunting-dog-leash-breaks.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/clydejohnson/a-little-lesson-in-karma/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">14b6a0f6-8dc1-4e55-b11c-ce4bb2698afa</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 17:57:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>